Sparks Photographs
undated
- Photographs, 1860-1997
  - Exterior of Maud MacKenzie’s mansion, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1274; 6 5/8 x 4 5/8 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Photograph of the exterior of Maud Sparks MacKenzie's mansion at Carmel, California.
    Photograph 01281 is a duplicate of this image.
  - Exterior of Maud MacKenzie’s mansion, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1275; Photographic print; 4 7/8 x 5 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Photograph of an exterior entrance to Maud Sparks MacKenzie's mansion in Carmel, California. There is a column at the corner of the builidng.
  - Man in a doorway of Maud MacKenzie’s mansion, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1276; Photographic print; 4 3/4 x 6 3/4 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Photograph of an indistinct man (possibly one of Benton Sparks' sons) standing in a doorway at Maud Sparks MacKenzie's mansion in Carmel, California.
  - Room of Maud MacKenzie’s mansion, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1277; Photographic print; 6 3/4 x 4 3/4 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Photograph of an interior room, possibly a bedroom, in Maud Sparks MacKenzie's mansion in Carmel, California.
  - Bedroom of Maud MacKenzie’s mansion, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1278; Photographic print; 6 3/4 x 4 3/4 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Photograph of a bedroom with a fireplace with a triangular mantle. The photograph was double exposed, but it is unclear what the second exposure depicts.
  - Exterior of Maud MacKenzie’s mansion, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1279; Photographic print; 6 3/4 x 4 3/4 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Photograph of the exterior of Maud Sparks MacKenzie's mansion at Carmel, California. There is a car parked at the end of the house with an unidentified man standing in front of it.
  - Exterior of Maud MacKenzie’s mansion, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1280; Photographic print; 6 1/2 x 4 5/8 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Photograph from above of the exterior of Maud Sparks MacKenzie's mansion at Carmel, California. The ocean and beach are visible behind the mansion. A car is parked at the edge of the house and there is a ladder leaning against one of the portions of the mansion.
    Photograph 00972 is a duplicate of this image.
  - Exterior of Maud MacKenzie’s mansion, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1281; Mounted photographic print; 6 1/2 x 4 3/8 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Photograph 01274 is a duplicate of this image.
  - Maud Sparks MacKenzie, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1282; Mounted photographic print; 3 3/8 x 1 3/4 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Partial photograph of Maud Sparks in a dress. The lower portion has been torn off.
  - Maud Sparks, circa 1883; UNRS-P2017-13_1283; Cabinet card; 4 1/4 x 6 3/8 (Box 9)
    Cabinet card of Maud Sparks as a girl. She is wearing a skirt and striped coat, holding a hat in her right hand and the rope of a swing in her left hand. Photograph taken by Kirkland. Handwritten on front: Maud Sparks.
    Cabinet card has been stored in a box with other cabinet cards from the collection.
  - Ada Ede Sparks, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1284; Photographic print; 1 1/2 x 1 7/8 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Portrait of Ada Ede Sparks wearing a dress. Handwritten on frame: Mrs. Ada Sparks, Benton H. Sparks.
  - Walter Ede, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1285; Glass plate; 8 x 10 (Box 8)
    Glass plate of a portrait of Walter Ede wearing a suit. The plate has a red matte surrounding the portrait. The plate was attached to a metal stand. Handwritten on the backing and frame: Walter Ede - Father of Ada Ede Sparks who married Benton H. Sparks. He was a rancher in Sierra Valley Calif.
  - Log building, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1286; Mounted photographic print; 7 3/4 x 4 3/4 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Photograph of a log cabin with a fence in front of it. One wall is made of flat boards.
  - Men standing in the lobby of the Overland Hotel, circa 1910s; UNRS-P2017-13_1287; Mounted photographic print; 8 5/8 x 6 1/2 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Photograph of a group of men sitting or standing in the lobby of the Overland Hotel. Handwritten on verso: Lobby of old Overland Hotel. Builder was Alec Dromiac (unsure of spelling) & friend of John Sparks. Mr. Dromiac asked Sparks to name the hotel & he did - OVERLAND HOTEL. in picture L to R. Charles Saddler who owned the business (but not Bldg), George Wingfield - mining millionaire (Goldfield & Tonopah), Man in middle with watch chian is Bob Perry who ran the stock yards.
  - Dog sitting in front of a Sparks family home in Georgetown, Texas, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1288; Mounted photographic print; 4 5/8 x 6 1/2 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Photograph of a dog sitting in front of a bench made out of antlers. There is a house in the background, which was the home of the Sparks family. Caption on front: old "Ed." Handwritten on verso: The old home just outside of Georgetown, Texas.
  - Lon Moore with a flour wagon, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1289; Mounted photographic print; 7 x 5 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Photograph of a Lon Moore, husband of Lillian Moore, standing next to two horses hitched to a cart. The side of the cart reads Olympic Flour. Handwritten on verso: Lon Moore - Portland Flouring Mill team.
  - Indian family appealing to Governor Sparks, circa 1906; UNRS-P2017-13_1290; Mounted photographic print; 7 x 5 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Photograph of Governor John Sparks standing next to an oval table talking with a Native American interpreter while four other Native Americans sit behind Sparks. Caption on front: Indian Johnny's Father, Mother, two sisters and an Interpreter appealing to Governor Sparks to save the life of their son and brother, who was executed for the crime of murder at the Nevada State Prison December 7, 1906.
  - Maud Sparks and a man at a Georgetown home of John Sparks, circa 1896; UNRS-P2017-13_1291; Mounted photographic print; 6 5/8 x 4 3/8 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Photograph of a Sparks family house in Georgetown, Texas. Maud Sparks MacKenzie is standing in the front yard next to an unidentified man. There are some decorative antler pieces in the front yard as well. Caption on front: Home of Capt. John Sparks Georgetown Tex 1896.
  - Alfred Sparks, circa 1914; UNRS-P2017-13_1292; Mounted photographic print; 3 1/2 x 5 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Photograph of Alfred Ede Sparks as a toddler. He is wearing a white garment, holding a small cup, and sitting on a small chair. Handwritten on verso: Alfred Ede Sparks. Photograph taken by Riverside Studio.
  - Two men and two women behind a paper mill cylinder, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1293; Mounted photographic print; 8 x 5 1/8 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Photograph of two men and two women standing behind a cylinder for a paper mill. The two women are looking at the camera and the men are working on the cylinder. Handwritten on verso: left to right Emma Hiff - unknow[n] and Allie [possibly Allie Burwitz]. (the men) They are repairing a cylinder in a paper mill in Bridal Veil, Oregon. Ordinarily they would have been sitting on the near side to repair it, but sat in the back for the picture.
  - Portrait of John Sparks circa 1875, UNRS-P2017-13_1294; Mounted photographic print; 5 5/8 x 8 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Photograph of a portrait of John Sparks. He is wearing a checkered suit and a dark tie. Handwritten on verso: Mrs. Nora Sparks. Picture of Mrs John Sparks. Photograph was mounted by Charles Lainer.
  - Portrait of John Sparks circa 1875, UNRS-P2017-13_1295; Mounted photographic print; 5 5/8 x 8 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Photograph of a profile portrait of John Sparks. He is wearing a checkered suit and a dark tie. Handwritten on verso: Mrs Nora Sparks picture of Mr John Sparks. Photograph was mounted by Charles Lainer.
  - Portrait of John Sparks circa 1903, UNRS-P2017-13_1296; Mounted photographic print; 4 1/8 x 6 7/8 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Photograph of John Sparks sitting at a desk. He has a pair of glasses in his left hand and a newspaper in his right hand. Handwritten on front: Thomson 1903.
  - Portrait of John Sparks circa 1904, UNRS-P2017-13_1297; Mounted photographic print; 4 x 6 1/2 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Photograph of a portrait of John Sparks wearing a suit, bowtie, and cowboy hat. Handwritten on front: Thomson 1904. Handwritten on verso: Grandpa Sparks (John Sparks) died 1908 - just under 65 years of age.
  - Portrait of John Sparks without mustache circa 1890, UNRS-P2017-13_1298; Mounted photographic print; 5 x 7 1/2 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Photograph of John Sparks without a mustache. He is wearing a suit, bowtie, and a long overcoat. Handwritten on verso: John Sparks - again w/out mustach. Photograph mounted by Taber.
  - Portrait of John Sparks without mustache circa 1890, UNRS-P2017-13_1299; Mounted photographic print; 5 1/4 x 6 3/4 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Photograph of John Sparks without a mustache. He is in profile sitting in a wooden chair wearing a suit. Handwritten on verso: Thornwall 1705 Birch. Photograph mounted by Taber.
  - John Sparks and Captain Dave, circa 1900, UNRS-P2017-13_1300; Mounted photographic print; 5 x 7 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Photograph of John Sparks standing next to a Native American man sitting in an antler chair. John Sparks is wearing a suit with a cowboy hat and the Native American man is wearing a suit with a badge on his left lapel. Handwritten on verso: Probably the Indian is "Captain Dave" the head man of the Washoe Tribe, with Gov. Sparks. Photograph mounted by Smith Studio.
  - Maud Sparks MacKenzie in her wedding dress, circa 1903; UNRS-P2017-13_1301; Mounted photographinc print; 3 x 7 1/4 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Photograph of Maud Sparks MacKenzie in her wedding dress. She is standing with her arms crossed behind her back. Photograph was taken by Dann.
  - Maud Sparks MacKenzie in her wedding dress, circa 1903; UNRS-P2017-13_1302; Mounted photographic print; 3 x 7 1/4 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Photograph of Maud Sparks MacKenzie in her wedding dress. She is holding a bunch of daisies in her hands and looking at them. Handwritten on verso: Maud Sparks. Photograph was taken by Dann.
  - Maud Sparks with a dog, circa 1900; UNRS-P2017-13_1303; Mounted photographic print; 3 x 7 1/4 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Photograph of Maud Sparks wearing a dress suit, blazer, and bowler cap. She is looking up at a spaniel which is sitting on a brick wall. Handwritten on verso: Maud Sparks. Photograph was taken by Dann.
  - Maud Sparks with a dog, circa 1900; UNRS-P2017-13_1304; Mounted photographic print; 3 x 7 1/4 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Photograph of Maud Sparks wearing a dress suit, blazer, and bowler cap. She is looking down at a spaniel which is sitting on a brick wall. Photograph was taken by Dann.
  - Maud Sparks, circa 1895; UNRS-P2017-13_1305; Mounted albumen; 5 1/4 x 8 1/2 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Photograph of Maud Sparks wearing a dress with a knit jacket, gloves, and a decorative hat. She is standing next to a stone wall. Handwritten on verso: Maud Sparks. Photograph by Falle.
  - Maud Sparks, circa 1890; UNRS-P2017-13_1306; Platinotype; 3 3/4 x 5 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Hand tinted portrait of Maud Sparks. Handwritten on verso: Maude Sparks (MacKenzie). Photograph was taken by Taber.
  - Charles Sparks, circa 1899; UNRS-P2017-13_1307; Mounted photographic print; 2 1/4 x 3 3/4 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Photograph of Charles Sparks wearing a suit and tie. Handwritten on verso: Charles M. Sparks. Photograph taken by the River Side Gallery.
  - Leland Sparks Sr. with two friends, August 1, 1908; UNRS-P2017-13_1308; Mounted photographic print; 5 x 3 3/4 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Photograph of Leland Sparks Sr. with two unidentified men. Handwritten on front: August 1st 1908. Photographer: H. Pierre Smith.
  - Charles Sparks, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1309; Mounted photographic print; 7 1/4 x 4 3/4 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Photograph of a group of men and women in front of an American flag. Leland Sparks Sr. is sitting in the third row fifth from the right. Charles Sparks is sitting in the center of the fourth row. Handwritten on verso: Uncle Charles Sparks seated center, in dark coat.
  - Canyon near Muddy River, circa 1905; UNRS-P2017-13_1310; Mounted photographic print; 3 3/8 x 3 1/2 (Box 7)
    Photograph of a field with a canyon in the background. There is a horse facing away from the camera in the foreground. Handwritten on verso: 1 Natural reservoir site in Muddy river near Moapa Salt Lake Route, Lincoln co., Nev.
    Photograph is stored in a smaller box with similar photographs.
  - Four men standing in a wheat field, circa 1905; UNRS-P2017-13_1311; Mounted photographic print; 3 1/2 x 3 1/2 (Box 7)
    Photograph of four men standing in a field of wheat. Handwritten on verso: 3 Field of wheat in May, sown and irrigated in Nev. Previous Sprolls Ranch, Muddy River, Lincoln Co., Nevada. Near Moapa on Salt Lake Route.
  - Men standing next to fig trees and grape vines, circa 1905; UNRS-P2017-13_1312; Mounted photographic print; 3 1/2 x 3 1/2 (Box 7)
    Photograph of men standing next to crops and trees. Handwritten on verso: 4 Fig trees and grape vines in Major Holt's vinyard. Muddy River, Lincoln Co., Nev. Near Moapa on Salt Lake Route.
  - Alfalfa field, circa 1905; UNRS-P2017-13_1313; Mounted photographic print; 3 1/2 x 3 1/2 (Box 7)
    Photograph of a field of alfalfa. Handwritten on verso: 6 Alfalfa field. Cobbs ranch Overton. Lincoln Co. Nev.
  - Four men in front of a fan palm tree, circa 1905; UNRS-P2017-13_1314; Mounted photographic print; 3 1/2 x 3 1/2 (Box 7)
    Photograph of four men standing in front of a fan plam. Handwritten on verso: 7 Fan palm tree at Cobbs ranch in Muddy River, Lincoln Co. Nev. near Overton.
  - Field of grapevines, circa 1905; UNRS-P2017-13_1315; Mounted photographic print; 3 1/2 x 3 1/2 (Box 7)
    Photograph of a field of grapevines. Handwritten on verso: 8 Prize seedless grape vineyard Mr. Gibson's ranch at St. Thomas on the Muddy River. Lincoln Co. Nev.
  - Man standing next to apricot trees, circa 1905; UNRS-P2017-13_1316; Mounted photographic print; 3 1/2 x 3 1/2 (Box 7)
    Photograph of a man standing next to a grove of trees. Handwritten on verso: 9 - Apricot trees, orchard on Sen. Clark's ranch. Las Vegas, Lincoln Co. Nev.
  - Adobe house with trees in front, circa 1905; UNRS-P2017-13_1317; Mounted photographic print; 3 1/2 x 3 1/2 (Box 7)
    Photograph of an adobe house with trees and a fence in front of it. Handwritten on verso: 10 Old adobe house. Las Vegas ranch, Lincoln Co. Nev.
  - Three men standing next to fig trees, circa 1905; UNRS-P2017-13_1318; Mounted photographic print; 3 1/2 x 3 1/2 (Box 7)
    Photograph of three men standing next to some trees. Handwritten on verso: 11 Fig trees. Sen. Clark's Las vegas ranch, Lincoln Co. Nev.
  - Four men next to an apricot tree, circa 1905; UNRS-P2017-13_1319; Mounted photographic print; 3 1/2 x 3 1/2 (Box 7)
    Photograph of four men underneath a tree. Handwritten on verso: 12 Largest apricot tree in the world. Twenty years old. 18 inches in diameter. Produced one ton of fruit in one season. Sen. Clark's Las Vegas ranch Lincoln Co, Nev.
  - Three men sitting under some trees, circa 1905; UNRS-P2017-13_1320; Mounted photographic print; 3 1/2 x 3 1/2 (Box 7)
    Photograph of three men sitting underneath some trees. Handwritten on verso: 13 Three "setters" in Las Vegas vineyard. Lincoln Co. Nev.
  - Two men outside the Las Vegas fort, circa 1905; UNRS-P2017-13_1321; Mounted photographic print; 3 1/2 x 3 1/2 (Box 7)
    Photograph of a man pointing at a brick wall with another man sitting on a tree root and writing. Handwritten on verso: 14 - The old Las Vegas fort, showing the port or rifle hole. The same being a part of the first smelter built west of the Mo. River. Erected for smelting lead ores from Potosi mine in Charleston Mt.
  - Main street in a small town, circa May 1905; UNRS-P2017-13_1322; Mounted photographic print; 3 1/2 x 3 1/2 (Box 7)
    Photograph of the main road in a town with some single story buildings on either side of the road. 15 Mr. Williams town. Las Vegas. Lincoln Co. Nev. May 1905.
  - Icing station in Las Vegas, circa May 1905; UNRS-P2017-13_1323; Mounted photographic print; 3 1/2 x 3 1/2 (Box 7)
    Photograph of an icing station in Las Vegas. Handwritten on verso: 16 Armour ice plant for icing fruit cars (West Side) Las Vegas New on Salt Lake route.
  - Armour icing station in Las Vegas, circa May 1905; UNRS-P2017-13_1324; Mounted photographic print; 3 1/2 x 3 1/2 (Box 7)
    Photograph of the Armour icing station in Las Vegas. Handwritten on verso: 17 Armour's ice plant (east side) Las Vegas Nev. For icing fruit cars on Salt Lake route.
  - People standing between trains, May 11, 1905; UNRS-P2017-13_1325; Mounted photographic print; 3 1/2 x 3 1/2 (Box 7)
    Photograph of people standing between trains. Handwritten on verso: 18 Salt Lake train at Las Vegas, Nev. May 11, 1905.
  - Man pointing towards some buildings, May 11, 1905; UNRS-P2017-13_1326; Mounted photographic print; 3 1/2 x 3 1/2 (Box 7)
    Photograph of a man in a suit and hat pointing at some buildings in the distance behind him. Handwritten on verso: 19 Truts at Las Vegas Nev. May 11 - 1905.
  - People standing around a train, circa May 1905; UNRS-P2017-13_1327; Mounted photographic print; 3 1/2 x 3 1/2 (Box 7)
    Photograph of some people standing around train cars. Handwritten on verso: 20 Depot car at Las Vegas Nev. May 1905.
  - People walking between a passenger and carrier train, circa May 1905; UNRS-P2017-13_1328; Mounted photographic print; 3 1/2 x 3 1/2 (Box 7)
    Photograph of men walking between two trains, one passenger and one carrier. Handwritten on verso: 21 Overland flyer Las Vegas Nev. May 1905. Salt Lake route.
  - Some men in front of a train station, circa May 1905; UNRS-P2017-13_1329; Mounted photographic print; 3 1/2 x 3 1/2 (Box 7)
    Photograph of some men standing outside a train station. Handwritten on verso: 22 Old depot Los Angeles. Salt Lake route. May 1905.
  - First Street bridge, Los Angeles, circa 1905; UNRS-P2017-13_1330; Mounted photographic print; 3 1/2 x 3 1/2 (Box 7)
    Photograph of a overpass for a road with houses and telephone poles visible at a lower level. In the foreground is the head of a man and a horse. Handwritten on verso: 24 On First St. bridge. Los Angeles, Cal.
  - Kiowa girls in elk tooth dresses, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1331; Cabinet card; 4 1/4 x 6 1/2 (Box 9)
    Cabinet card of two Native American girls of the Kiowa tribe wearing elk tooth dresses. One of them is sitting on a chair covered by a fur. Handwritten on verso [twice: once in pencil and once in pen]: Little Kiowa girls Elk tooth dresses Value $500.00 apiece. Photographer: Irwin.
  - Kiowa Annie, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1332; Cabinet card; 4 1/4 x 6 1/2 (Box 9)
    Cabinet card of a young Native American woman of the Kiowa tribe wearing an elk tooth dress. She is posed with her hands behind her head. Handwritten on verso [twice: once in pencil and once in pen]: Kiowa Annie elk tooth dress value $1000.00.
  - Quanah Parker with two squaws, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1333; Cabinet card; 4 1/4 x 6 1/2 (Box 9)
    Cabinet card of a Native American chieftan between two Native American women. They are standing on the front porch of a building. Handwritten on verso: Quanah Parker with two of his six Squaws. Chief of the Comanche Indians. Photographer: Irwin.
  - Horse named Bonaparte with a trainer, September 24, 1890; UNRS-P2017-13_1334; Mounted photographic print; 3 3/4 x 4 3/4 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Photograph of a horse with a horse trainer at his head holding the reins. Handwritten on verso: Pucheron Norman, "Boneparte" 7 yr. Sweepstakes Nevada State Fair Reno 9-24-90, Compliments of Fred Stadtmuller.
  - Buildings at Hubbard Ranch, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1335; Mounted photographic print; 4 5/8 x 3 5/8 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Photograph of ranch buildings and some fences. Handwritten on front: Hubbard Ranch.
  - Ranching sheds, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1336; Mounted photographic print; 4 5/8 x 3 5/8 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Photograph of ranch sheds. There are horses eating at a trough in front of the shed. Handwritten on front: Saujacinto sheds.
  - Sparks mining boat on the Snake River, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1337; Mounted photographic print; 4 3/4 x 3 5/8 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Photograph of a mining boat on the Snake River belonging to the Sparks family. Handwritten on verso: Sparks Mining Boat on Snake River.
  - Corporal James Emmett Shrigerland on horseback, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1338; Mounted photographic print; 3 3/4 x 4 3/4 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Photograph of a young soldier named James Emmett Shrigerland in uniform on a horse. The soldier is holding an American Flag. Handwritten on verso: Yours Sincerely, Corporal James Emmett Shrigerland.
  - K. B. Armour, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1339; Mounted photographic print; 4 x 5 7/8 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Photograph of a portrait of an older man. He is wearing a suit and tie. Caption attached to photograph: My friend, K. B. Armour. Photographer: D. P. Thomson.
  - C. R. Thomas, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1340; Mounted photographic print; 4 x 5 7/8 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Photograph of a portrait of an older man wearing a suit and tie. Handwritten on verso: C R Thomas [?] sec. order. Photographer: D. P. Thomson.
  - Man and pony in a corral, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1341; Mounted photographic print; 8 x 4 7/8 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Photograph of a man holding the lead to a small pony. They are standing in a corral with trees in the background.
  - Elk at the Sparks Alamo Ranch, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1342; Mounted photographic print; 8 x 4 7/8 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Photograph of three elk belonging to John Sparks standing next to a wooden ranch building. There is a male, female, and young elk. Their names are Billie, Kate, and Bess.
  - Two men standing in front of a house, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1343; Mounted photographic print; 8 x 4 7/8 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Photograph of a two story house with two men standing in front of it. Between the men is a dog sitting on a stool and a bird in a cage on top of a ladder. No identification.
  - House in Burnet, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1344; Mounted photographic print; 8 x 4 7/8 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Photograph of a single story stone house with a fence around it. There are palm trees along the road with support cages around them. There are some people standing on the front porch of the house. Handwritten on front: Our house in Burnet. Handwritten on verso: in Texas.
  - Sparks Alamo Ranch house with John Sparks’ kids in front, circa 1892; UNRS-P2017-13_1345; Mounted photographic print; 8 x 4 7/8 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Photograph of the Sparks ranch house in Reno, Nevada, with Leland Sr., Charles, and Benton in front of the fence and Nancy Elnora and an unidentified woman behind it. Handwritten on verso: another view of our Reno home with Benton, Charlie, & Leland outside the fence. From Mama.
  - James Williby on horseback, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_1346; Mounted photographic print; 8 x 4 7/8 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Photograph of a man named James Williby sitting horseback. Handwritten on verso: Jas Williby worker for Jno Sparks in Wyoming & Nevada in 1878 to 1882 after which doh he joined Buffalo Bill's Wild West which Morwich Mess Laleou Sruich the famous rifle shot of the world. Photographer: Kid. Created by Kirkland studios.
  - People standing on the porch of the Sparks Alamo Ranch house, circa 1892; UNRS-P2017-13_1347; Mounted photographic print; 8 x 4 7/8 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Photograph of the Sparks ranch house in Reno, Nevada. There are two women sitting on the porch (one of whom is Nancy Elnora), two men standing in front of the porch, and two boys sitting on the steps (possibly Leland Sr. and Benton). Charles is standing in front of another man on the other side of the porch. Handwritten on verso: Front-friew of our Reno home, from Mama.
  - Nancy Lee and Allie Sparks, circa 1924; UNRS-P2017-13_1348; Photographic print; 4 x 6 3/4 (Box 3, Folder 4)